const questions = [
    {
        question: "What's Bitta's last name?",
        op1: "Edison",
        op2: "Bennet",
        op3: "Barry",
        op4: "Barnes",
        correct: "Perry",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many episodes does season 1 have?",
        op1: "21",
        op2: "18",
        op3: "22",
        op4: "24",
        correct: "25",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What's Abed's racial background?",
        op1: "Indian and Polish",
        op2: "Arab and German",
        op3: "Indian and Slovenian",
        op4: "Arab and Indian",
        correct: "Arab and Polish",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What does Pierce's dad's company sells?",
        op1: "Napkins",
        op2: "Toilette Paper",
        op3: "Dish Towels",
        op4: "Sanitizing Wipes",
        correct: "Moist Towelettes",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the app students of Greendale used to rate each other?",
        op1: "WoofWoofBeenz",
        op2: "GreedaleStars",
        op3: "FiveStars",
        op4: "CheeChoowCheeChoow",
        correct: "MeowMeowBeenz",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Dean's weird fetish?",
        op1: "Brazilian Birds",
        op2: "German Shepards",
        op3: "Jeff",
        op4: "Labradors",
        correct: "Dalmatians",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many children does Shirley have?",
        op1: "1",
        op2: "2",
        op3: "4",
        op4: "None",
        correct: "3",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is Abed's girlfirend's name?",
        op1: "Raquel",
        op2: "Rosie",
        op3: "Ruth",
        op4: "Rita",
        correct: "Rachel",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is Troy's monkey's name?",
        op1: "King Kong",
        op2: "Britta's Boobs",
        op3: "Fivel",
        op4: "Bruno",
        correct: "Annie's Boobs",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the interactive VCR game Abed and Annie play?",
        op1: "Dungeons and Dragons",
        op2: "Pile of Guns",
        op3: "Whose Ears are These?",
        op4: "Bang!",
        correct: "Pile of Bullets",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What's Abed's favorite food?",
        op1: "Salmon",
        op2: "Splingles",
        op3: "Kettle Corn",
        op4: "Pizza",
        correct: "Buttered Noodles",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of Greendale's most dangerous criminal?",
        op1: "Butt Crack Psycho",
        op2: "Coin Bandit",
        op3: "Ass Cheek Robber",
        op4: "Benjamin Chang",
        correct: "Ass Crack Bandit",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Who are the winners of the first and sacond Paintball game, respectively?",
        op1: "Jeff and Jeff",
        op2: "Britta and Pierce",
        op3: "Jeff and Shirley",
        op4: "Chang and Shirley",
        correct: "Jeff and Pierce",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What's the name of Greendale's drama teacher?",
        op1: "Professor Professorson",
        op2: "Professor Peter Sheffield",
        op3: "Professor Ian Duncan",
        op4: "Professor Noel Cornwallis",
        correct: "Professor Sean Garrity",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which member of the Study Group is, according to Pierce, his favorite?",
        op1: "Jeff",
        op2: "Shirley",
        op3: "Troy",
        op4: "Britta",
        correct: "Annie",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Where is Rich, from pottery class, from?",
        op1: "Denver",
        op2: "New Jersey",
        op3: "Albuquerque",
        op4: "San Francisco",
        correct: "Santa Fe",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many times has Pierce been married?",
        op1: "Three",
        op2: "One",
        op3: "Five",
        op4: "Eight",
        correct: "Seven",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Troy's favorite celebrity?",
        op1: "Jim Belushi",
        op2: "Chevy Chase",
        op3: "Cristian Bale",
        op4: "Sophie B Hawkins",
        correct: "LeVar Burton",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which fast food chain (almost) buys Greendale?",
        op1: "McDonald's",
        op2: "KFC",
        op3: "In-N-Out Burger",
        op4: "Taco Bell",
        correct: "Subway",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What's Abed's favortite TV show?",
        op1: "Cougar Town",
        op2: "Cougarton Abbey",
        op3: "The Cape",
        op4: "Doctor Who",
        correct: "Inspector Spacetime",
        stage: 1
    },
    {
        question: "",
        op1: "",
        op2: "",
        op3: "",
        op4: "",
        correct: "",
        stage: 2
    }

]